SEBASTIAN ŚI FDŹ

WFB DFSIGNER & DEVELOPER

Location London, UK

Contact

sebastian.sledz@gmail.com +44 754 333 1829



ABOUT ME

I specialize in web design and coding in HTML/CSS and related stack I can easily work on jquery/javascript scripts, implement sites in Wordpress or other CMS. I love to broaden my skills and train actively within above areas but I also explore different fields. Currently I am focused on development in JavaScript and Vue.js applications. I work mainly in Visual Studio but as I don't limit my interests I have a good knowledge of Adobe Creative Suit and a variety of apps that prove helpful during creations. I got to know approaches and frameworks such as Bootstrap, Materialize, MDL, Jekyll, Hugo, Git via Git Hub, Scrum/Agile, additional ways of data handling or programming like REST, XML, JSON, PHP, C# and some more. I believe good design is within a grasp, for this reason I like to think beyond colors and layout to consider the motivations of users so I can help make their interaction with the design vibrant and intuitive.





WORK EXPERIENCE

GREEN HERRING STUDIO

Web Designer and Developer, 2010-current

Here begins my freelance experience as a Graphic and Web Designer. For fun, as a volunteer or for commercial clients I prepared a variety of works from posters and illustrations through animations and flash banners to responsive web sites and some branding designs.

FLEX FUNDING

Web Designer and Developer, 2016-current

I am responsible for development of company website, branding materials for web and print, making resources for promotion and related to company business. I am working mostly with HTML/CSS, IS, PHP and in Adobe Creative Suite.

CITI INTERNATIONAL

Database Analyst, 2014-2016

Working on object-relational databases I am reporting with Visual Basic and SQL Reporting Services.



EDUCATION

WARSAW SCHOOL OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Warsaw, Poland 2015-2016 Web Database Applications

UNIVERSITY OF FINANCE AND MANAGEMENT

Warsaw, Poland 2004-2010 Psychology



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0
Adobe Illustrator	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0
Adobe After Effects	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0
Visual Studio	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0
PHP	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0
HTML&CSS	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0
Javascript	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0
SQL	•	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0



PERSONAL SKILLS

Social Commitment	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0
Organization	•	•	•	•	•	•	O	0	0
Creativity	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•
Communication	•	•	•	O	O	•	0	0	0
Positive Attitude	•	•	•					•	•



LANGUAGES

Polish (native)	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•
English	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0	0
Russian	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0



COURSES

IBM: MOBILE APPLICATION SPECIALIST

Warsaw, 2016

This course was a complete guide to mobile application development. I learned about programming with HTML5 and Dojo Mobile, ¡Query scripting or working with IBM Worklight.

MICROSOFT: PROGRAMMING WITH C#

Warsaw, 2015

This course provided a solid foundation in object-oriented programming knowledge. This was my introduction to the C# and the world of .NET which I continue on postgraduate studies



HOBBIES AND ACTIVITIES



Bicycle riding





Photography



Travelling

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2002, item 1182 as amended.